Have you ever dreamt of strolling along the streets of Venice, climbing the Eiffel Tower or flying above the Grand Canyon?
你是否曾梦想过漫步在威尼斯的街道上，攀登埃菲尔铁塔，或者飞越大峡谷上空？
It's much easier to take a virtual holiday now than ever before.
如今，享受虚拟假期比以往任何时候都要容易得多。
Doesn't it sound adventurous – travelling to breathtaking destinations around the world while never leaving the comfort of your own home?
这听起来不新奇刺激吗——足不出户，就能前往世界各地令人惊叹的目的地旅行？
Digital maps let you roam almost any location on the planet, meaning you can explore the night markets in Bangkok, hover over mountainous regions like the Himalayas or zoom in on tiny islands and imagine you're sunbathing and smelling the sea.
数字地图让你可以漫游地球上几乎任何地方，这意味着你可以探索曼谷的夜市，在喜马拉雅山脉等山区上空盘旋，或者聚焦于小岛，想象自己在享受日光浴、闻着海风的味道。
Of course, you won't experience the weather and culture in exactly the same way, but at least it's an option.
当然，你无法以完全相同的方式体验天气和文化，但至少这是一个选择。
If you are a nature lover, it's possible to take an interactive virtual tour, with the option of virtual commentary, of a national park like Yellowstone in the USA.
如果你是自然爱好者，可以参加美国黄石国家公园等地的互动式虚拟游览，并选择虚拟解说。
This area has a lot of volcanic activity, so you can watch geysers erupt, see sulphur lakes and virtually hike iconic trails.
该地区火山活动频繁，因此你可以观看间歇泉喷发，观赏硫磺湖，并虚拟徒步标志性的小径。
Their website is full of videos walking you to famous viewpoints like Dragon's Mouth Spring and the cascading waterfall at Upper Falls.
他们的网站上有很多视频，带你前往龙口泉和上瀑布的层叠瀑布等著名观景点。
And then there are oceanic adventures too.
此外，还有海洋探险。
National Geographic offers virtual underwater experiences so you can dive with sharks and other marine life, see coral reefs come alive and explore sunken shipwrecks.
《国家地理》提供虚拟水下体验，让你可以与鲨鱼和其他海洋生物一起潜水，观赏生机勃勃的珊瑚礁，探索沉没船只。
You can now tour many museums and landmarks virtually too, like The British Museum in London.
现在，你还可以虚拟游览许多博物馆和地标建筑，例如伦敦的大英博物馆。
You can explore more than 60 galleries where you'll see priceless artefacts from around the world, like the Rosetta Stone, and famous paintings and sculptures.
你可以探索60多个展厅，在那里你会看到来自世界各地的无价文物，如罗塞塔石碑，以及著名的绘画和雕塑。
The Taj Mahal is another place you can visit virtually and at a 360-degree angle, so you can scale heights that would be almost impossible if you were there in person.
泰姬陵是另一个可以虚拟参观的地方，并且可以360度视角观看，因此你可以到达几乎不可能亲身到达的高度。
They say 'the world is your oyster'.
人们常说"世界是你的牡蛎"。
So next time you get the travel bug, try a virtual escape.
所以下次你燃起旅行欲望时，试试虚拟逃离吧。
A shoestring budget is no problem – you can still explore the world, and you don't even need a passport.
预算有限也没问题——你仍然可以探索世界，甚至不需要护照。